<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Great Mall Guide</string>
    <string name="MensClothing">Mens Clothing</string>
    <string name="Clothing">Clothing</string>
    <string name="WomensClothing">Womens Clothing</string>
    <string name="Shoe">Shoes</string>
    <string name="Electronics">Electronics</string>
    <string name="Entertainment">Entertainment</string>
    <string name="Food">Food</string>
    <string name="Jewelry">Jewelry</string>
    <string name="Specialty">Specialty</string>

    <string name="AbercrombieName">Abercrombie</string>
    <string name="AdidasName">Adidas</string>
    <string name="AeropostaleName">Aeropostale</string>
    <string name="AldoName">Aldo</string>
    <string name="AmericanEagleName">American Eagle</string>
    <string name="AndersenBakeryName">Anderson\'s Bakery</string>
    <string name="ArmaniExchangeName">Armani Exchange</string>
    <string name="AuntieAnneName">Auntie Anne\'s</string>
    <string name="BananaRepublicName">Banana Republic</string>
    <string name="BathBodyWorksName">Bath and Body Works</string>
    <string name="BeautyPalaceName">Beauty Palace</string>
    <string name="BebeName">Bebe</string>
    <string name="BedBathName">Bed Bath and Beyond</string>
    <string name="BevmoName">Bevmo</string>
    <string name="BoseName">Bose</string>
    <string name="BounceRamaName">Bounce-A-Rama</string>
    <string name="BurlingtonName">Burlington</string>
    <string name="CajunGrillName">Cajun Grill</string>
    <string name="CalvinKleinName">Calvin Klein</string>
    <string name="CenturyTheatresName">Century Theatres</string>
    <string name="ChampsName">Champs</string>
    <string name="ChipotleName">Chipotle</string>
    <string name="CinnabonName">Cinnabon</string>
    <string name="ClairesName">Claires</string>
    <string name="CoachName">Coach</string>
    <string name="ColdStoneName">Cold Stone</string>
    <string name="ColumbiaName">Columbia</string>
    <string name="CottonOnName">Cotton On</string>
    <string name="CrocsName">Crocs</string>
    <string name="DaveBusterName">Dave and Busters</string>
    <string name="DippinDotsName">Dippin Dots</string>
    <string name="DKNYName">DKNY</string>
    <string name="ExpressName">Express</string>
    <string name="FamousFootwearName">Famous Footwear</string>
    <string name="FinishLineName">Finish Line</string>
    <string name="FootLockerName">Foot Locker</string>
    <string name="Forever21Name">Forever 21</string>
    <string name="GameStopName">GameStop</string>
    <string name="GapName">Gap</string>
    <string name="GhirardelliName">Ghirardelli</string>
    <string name="GNCName">GNC</string>
    <string name="HMName">HM</string>
    <string name="HollisterName">Hollister</string>

    <string name="AbercromieDescription">For over 100 years we have dedicated ourselves to designing and producing the highest quality All-American clothing. However, as we continue to create the coolest clothes, counterfeiters are making cheap knockoffs that are often mistaken for the real deal. The only way to be sure you\'re buying genuine Abercrombie and Fitch gear is from one of our stores or websites.</string>
    <string name="AdidasDescription">We carry everything for your fitness needs! From basketball jerseys to hats and bags, we have it all! Kids footwear in toddler, grade-school and preschool sizes. Women\'s footwear and sport apparel, men\'s footwear and sport apparel. Shorts, sports bras and performance tees made with Playdry designed to keep your body cool and dry while you work out! Come on by today!! The sport of fitness has arrived!</string>
    <string name="AeropostaleDescription">A popular shopping destination for today\'s teenagers, Aéropostale is a leading mall-based specialty retailer that designs, markets and sells its own brand of casual, current apparel targeting 14 to 18 year-olds. Aéropostale provides their customers with high-quality fashion and basic merchandise at unquestionable value and compelling prices. Aéropostale\'s collection includes staples like their famous polos, hoodies, jeans and graphic tees as well as essentials such as dormwear, jewelry, footwear and swimwear. Aéropostale maintains their own ecommerce site, aeropostale.com, which offers extended sizes and additional Aéropostale product. The first Aéropostale store was opened in 1987.</string>
    <string name="Aldo">Aldo Shoes is an upscale shoe store with offerings for both men and women.</string>
    <string name="AldoDescription">Aldo Shoes is an upscale shoe store with offerings for both men and women.</string>
    <string name="AmericanEagleDescription">AE brings you high quality, on-trend clothing, accessories and personal care products at affordable prices. AE\'s collection includes modern basics like jeans, surplus and graphic tees as well as a stylish assortment of cool accessories, outerwear, footwear and swimwear. We target men and women ages 15 to 25, but welcome individuals of all ages everywhere. Live your life. </string>
    <string name="AndersenBakeryDescription">We continue the tradition of baking pastries and breads that create authentic European taste and quality.</string>
    <string name="ArmaniExchangeDescription">Armani Exchange is the youthful label created by iconic Italian designer Giorgio Armani, offering men\'s and women\'s clothing and accessories that are inspired by the designer\'s codes of style. Armani Exchange captures the heritage of the Armani brand through a modern sensibility.</string>
    <string name="AuntieAnneDescription">Auntie Anne\'s provides 11 varieties of hot, fresh pretzel products, in sweet and zesty flavors. It\'s only natural to want to try one! And nothing goes better with your pretzel than one of our dips and our Old Fashioned Lemonade™. There\'s nothing to lose because Auntie Anne\'s has a pretzel perfect guarantee. Auntie Anne\'s guarantees you\'ll love your pretzel or they will replace it with one that you do. Yes, that may seem a little gutsy, but when you\'ve rolled, twisted and baked over a billion pretzels (that\'s 1,000,000,000) there\'s a pretty good track record. Check out www.auntieannes.com for additional information on Auntie Anne\'s.</string>
    <string name="BananaRepublicDescription">Banana Republic Factory Stores offer adult formal and casual attire for any occasion and for many needs.</string>
    <string name="BathBodyWorksDescription">Bath and Body Works is the apothecary of the 21st century. It is the authority dedicated to helping people find their own individual paths to well-being by bringing them the very best personal care products the world has to offer. Every item in more than 1,700 Bath and Body Works stores nationwide is created to help nourish the spirit, bring a sense of balance, and leave the customer feeling beautiful inside and out.</string>
    <string name="BeautyPalaceDescription">One of the premier tenants of the Great Mall. Part salon, part beauty supply extravaganza, Beauty Palace offers a large selection of products and services to make you look your best. Hair and skin care bottles from Crew, bareMinerals, Enjoy, Dermalogica, and Biolage overrun the shelves while Gladys, the beautician, performs everything from haircuts and Japanese perms to eyebrow waxing in the back.</string>
    <string name="BebeDescription">Designed for women who are passionate about fashion and their own unique style, the bebe brand combines the bold sexiness of today\'s trends, with the excitement and fun of a fast-paced lifestyle.</string>
    <string name="BedBathBeyondDescription">Founded in 1971, Bed Bath and Beyond Inc. is a nationwide chain of superstores selling predominantly better quality domestics merchandise and home furnishings. Bed Bath and Beyond combines superior service and a huge selection of items at everyday low prices within a constantly evolving shopping environment that has proven to be both fun and exciting for customers.</string>
    <string name="BevmoDescription">BevMo! stores provide an inviting and entertaining environment. Friendly, product-knowledgeable salespeople offer customers individual service and advice as they explore the store\'s vast product offering. There is a strong element of fun and discovery as customers sample wines, beers and specialty foods, often in tandem with personal appearances by noted winemakers.</string>
    <string name="BoseDescription">What makes a Bose Store experience so unique? It\'s more than just the innovative products you\'ll see. It\'s the excitement of a live demonstration, the one-on-one attention from our dedicated Sales Specialists, and the knowledge you gain with each visit. It\'s the breadth of our products, the custom installations and the ongoing support that keeps Bose customers coming back. If you\'re interested in Bose products, then come discover them like never before. Visit the Bose Store and experience something special.</string>
    <string name="BounceARamaDescription">Welcome to a world of fun. From our inflatable jumpers and slides to our exciting arcade area, we\'ve created a world your family will love. Grab the kids and come visit!</string>
    <string name="BurlingtonDescription">At Burlington Coat Factory, you\'ll find a large assortment of current, high-quality, designer and name-brand merchandise at up to 70% off department store prices. Choose from a large selection of coats, clothing, and shoes for the entire family. And don\'t forget our great assortment of linens and home décor, PLUS everything you need for baby, from baby bottles to cribs! Burlington Coat Factory -- a convenient one-stop shopping experience with the labels you love, at prices you\'ll love even more! </string>
    <string name="CajunGrillDescription">Cue up the zydeco, it\'s time for a trip to the Gulf Coast. If you like your fish blackened and your chicken peppered, you\'re in luck. Finish up with a heaping helping of red beans and rice. But watch out for alligators.</string>
    <string name="CalvinKleinDesciption">Top fashion for men and women, from the world renound designer, Calvin Klein.</string>
    <string name="CenturyTheatresDescription">Twenty theaters and a bucket of popcorn will help you forget about the outside world for 90 minutes. Add Real 3-D to the equation, and you\'ll enter another realm altogether.</string>
    <string name="ChampsDescription">Champs Sports, a member of the Foot Locker, Inc. (NYSE: FL) family, is one of the largest mall-based specialty athletic footwear and apparel retailers in North America. Its product categories include athletic footwear, apparel and accessories. This combination allows Champs Sports to differentiate itself from other mall-based stores by presenting complete product assortments for the sports lifestyle enthusiast. Its more than 540 stores are located throughout the United States, Puerto Rico and Canada.</string>
    <string name="ChopotleDescription">At Chipotle, we aim to do a few things but do them exceptionally well. When Chipotle first opened its doors in 1993, the goal was simple: to serve high quality, delicious food quickly with an experience that not only exceeded, but redefined the fast food experience.</string>
    <string name="CinnabonDescription">Cinnabon bakeries have built a reputation for serving fresh, aromatic cinnamon rolls made with premium Indonesian cinnamon and topped with a sweet, rich, cream cheese-based frosting. Each Cinnabon product is served hot out of the oven and baked fresh before our guest\'s eyes. Cinnabon\'s commitment to premium ingredients and quality has paid off. Cinnabon bakeries have been named the #1 restaurant chain in the USA by an ePinions® online poll. Additionally, Cinnabon was named one of the top 50 pleasures in life by Expansion Magazine, the most influential business magazine in all of Mexico.</string>
    <string name="ClairesDescription">Claire\'s Stores, Inc. is a leading international specialty retailer offering value-priced costume jewelry, accessories and cosmetics to fashion-aware tweens, teens and young adults.</string>
    <string name="CoachDescription">Coach is a modern American luxury brand with a rich heritage rooted in quality and craftsmanship. All over the world, the Coach name is synonymous with the ease and sophistication of New York style.</string>
    <string name="ColdStoneDescription">If it has anything to do with ice cream, it has everything to do with Cold Stone Creamery. From unique ice cream creations to root beer floats, cakes and shakes- nobody serves up the ultimate indulgence like Cold Stone. We also offer catering and fundraising opportunities. Contact us today!</string>
    <string name="ColumbiaDescription">Columbia, the flagship brand of Portland, Oregon-based Columbia Sportswear Company, has been creating innovative apparel, footwear, accessories and equipment for outdoor enthusiasts since 1938. Columbia has become a leading global brand by channeling the company\'s passion for the outdoors, and an innovative spirit of “trying stuff”, into technologies and performance products that keep people warm, dry, cool and protected year-round.</string>
    <string name="CottonOnDescription">The Cotton On Group is a retail powerhouse renowned for its winning combination of globally relevant fashion for men and women at affordable prices. It all began back in 1991 with one store in Geelong, Victoria, Australia . From modest beginnings, Cotton On has quickly evolved into a bona fide fashion destination boasting in excess of 500 stores and 5500 employees. The original Cotton On offer has expanded to successfully branch into intimates, sleepwear and activewear with Cotton On Body; children\'s fashion with Cotton On Kids, footwear with Rubi shoes; and gifts and stationary with Typo. With a significant presence in Australia, New Zealand, Singapore, Hong Kong, Malaysia and the US, we have a vision to open stores into the thousands in the coming 5 years, Cotton On Group is taking the world by storm.</string>
    <string name="CrocsDescription">Crocs, Inc, a world leader in innovative casual footwear for men, women and children, celebrated its 10th anniversary in 2012. Crocs offers several distinct shoe collections with more than 300 four-season footwear styles. All Crocs™ shoes feature Croslite™ material, a proprietary, revolutionary technology that gives each pair of shoes the soft, comfortable, lightweight and odor-resistant qualities that Crocs fans know and love. Crocs fans “Get Crocs Inside” every pair of shoes, from the iconic clog to new sneakers, sandals, boots and heels. Since its inception in 2002, Crocs has sold more than 200 million pairs of shoes in more than 90 countries around the world. </string>
    <string name="DaveBusterDecription">People are our greatest strength. We hire the best talent. We train, motivate and empower them in an environment where everyone has the opportunity to flourish. We unleash their potential and recognize and reward their contributions.Respect and Caring for our guests and each other, as people diverse in background and perspective, as a team and as members of the communities we serve. Honesty and Integrity. We will conduct ourselves in an open, honest and fair manner building trust in all of our working relationships. Teamwork. We believe the team is stronger than the individual. We build on each other\'s ideas and talents because we know that together we make better decisions and experience more success. Service is our passion. We go above and beyond to create loyalty one guest at a time. Excellence. An unwavering commitment to quality and innovation. We constantly raise the bar in all that we do to sustain our competitive advantage. Fun is essential to our success. For our guests and for ourselves.</string>
    <string name="DippinDotsDescription">Dippin\' Dots presents a new twist to your old ice cream favorites with our Dot Delicacies line of Ice Cream Cakes and Sandwiches. Each Cake features a different Dippin\' Dots flavor, blended with rich cake pieces, drizzled with creamy sauces, on a crunchy cookie or a chocolaty fudge crust. They\'re the perfect treat for fun party. </string>
    <string name="DKNYDescription">Simply stated, DKNY is the energy and spirit of New York. International, eclectic, fun, fast and real. DKNY addresses the real-life needs of people everywhere, from work to weekend, jeans to evening. Both fashionable and friendly, DKNY consistently delivers its unique mix of style around the world.</string>
    <string name="ExpressDescription">EXPRESS is a specialty apparel and accessories retailer of women\'s and men\'s merchandise, targeting the 20 to 30 year old customer. The Company has over 30 years of experience offering a distinct combination of fashion and quality at an attractive value, addressing needs across work, casual, jeanswear, and going-out occasions. The Company currently operates more than 600 retail and factory outlet stores, located primarily in high-traffic shopping malls, lifestyle centers, and street locations across the United States, Canada, and Puerto Rico. EXPRESS merchandise is also available at franchise locations in the Middle East, Latin America, and South Africa. The Company also markets and sells its products through the Company\'s e-commerce website, www.express.com, as well as its mobile app for iOS and Android.</string>
    <string name="FamousFootwearDescription">At Famous Footwear we know shoes are more than just something you put on your feet. Wearing the right shoe helps you make the most of every day. That\'s why we have fantastic brand name shoes at great values for women, men and kids. With over 950 stores nationwide, we\'re committed to providing you with the brands you demand at prices you deserve. At Famous Footwear, you\'ll find the hottest brands including Nike, Puma, adidas, New Balance, ASICS, Steve Madden, DC Shoes, Skechers, Converse and so many more! See where our shoes can take you today. Make today Famous. Famous Footwear is part of the Brown Shoe Company (NYSE: BWS), the leading consumer-driven footwear company in the country. Brown Shoe\'s been making and selling shoes for over 130 years, and, along with our exclusive brand partners including Naturalizer, LifeStride, Carlos by Carlos Santana, Franco Sarto, Etienne Aigner, Dr. Scholl\'s, Nickels Soft and Buster Brown, we pride ourselves on quality and excellent service.</string>
    <string name="FinishLineDescription">Finish Line is a leading athletic retailer offering the best selection of brand name footwear, apparel and accessories. The company operates more than 660 stores in 47 states and online at www.finishline.com. We offer the best selection of premium brands and styles—delivering a relevant product assortment that connects with our customers\' dynamic lifestyle. This premium experience, for our consumers, is driven by quality and not price. Our assortment is focused on everyday sport footwear, products that are made for sport but primarily worn for fashion or every day use, but we also carry the best performance and athletic casual footwear in the mall and online. We compliment this best-in-class footwear selection with the right mix of premium apparel and accessories.</string>
    <string name="FootLockerDescription">Foot Locker is the world\'s leading retailer of athletic footwear and apparel. Headquartered in New York City, it operates approximately 3,900 athletic retail stores in 17 countries in North America, Europe and Australia.</string>
    <string name="Forever21Description">At Forever 21, style isn\'t dictated…It\'s inspired. Forever 21 is the leading fashion retailer of the latest trends and the season\'s hottest styles at can\'t-resist-prices. U.S. and international locations stay true to the fast-fashion destination\'s iconic store aesthetic giving fashion fans all over the globe the unforgettable shopping experience that is the one and only Forever 21.</string>
    <string name="GanmeStopDescription">GameStop sells the most popular new software, hardware and game accessories for the PC and next generation game console systems from Sony, Nintendo, Microsoft and Sega and is also the industry\'s largest reseller of pre-played games.</string>
    <string name="GapDescription">Apparel and accessories for the entire family! Exceptional Value, Affordable Style!</string>
    <string name="GhirardelliDescription">Ghirardelli is one of the few companies in America that controls the entire chocolate manufacturing process, from cocoa bean to finished product. This control over the manufacturing process, combined with Ghirardelli\'s proprietary bean blend and unique methods of roasting and processing, ensures that you are rewarded with the highest quality and richest products.</string>
    <string name="GNCDescription">GNC sets the standard in the health and nutrition industry by demanding truth in labeling, ingredient safety and product potency, all while remaining on the cutting edge of nutritional science. General Nutrition Centers is the world\'s largest company of its kind devoted exclusively to helping its customers improve their quality of life.</string>
    <string name="HMDescription">HM is one of the worlds leading fashion retailers, offering our customers fashion and quality at the best price. We offer a wide range of clothing, with everything from basics to the latest fashion trends. With new items arriving in the stores daily, customers will always be surprised by the fresh selection of merchandise.</string>
    <string name="HollisterDescription">Our unique lifestyle is felt through the energy of our in-store experience. We\'ve dedicated ourselves to designing and producing the highest quality SoCal inspired clothing</string>


</resources>
