<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Project2</string>
    <string name="AbercrombieName">Abercrombie</string>
    <string name="AdidasName">Adidas</string>
    <string name="AeropostaleName">Aeropostale</string>
    <string name="AldoName">Aldo</string>
    <string name="AmericanEagleName">American Eagle</string>
    <string name="AndersenBakeryName">Anderson\'s Bakery</string>
    <string name="ArmaniExchangeName">Armani Exchange</string>
    <string name="AuntieAnneName">Auntie Anne\'s</string>
    <string name="BananaRepublicName">Banana Republic</string>
    <string name="BathBodyWorksName">Bath and Body Works</string>
    <string name="BeautyPalaceName">Beauty Palace</string>
    <string name="BebeName">Bebe</string>
    <string name="BedBathName">Bed Bath and Beyond</string>
    <string name="BevmoName">Bevmo</string>
    <string name="BoseName">Bose</string>
    <string name="BounceRamaName">Bounce-A-Rama</string>
    <string name="BurlingtonName">Burlington</string>
    <string name="AbercromieDescription">For over 100 years we have dedicated ourselves to designing and producing the highest quality All-American clothing. However, as we continue to create the coolest clothes, counterfeiters are making cheap knockoffs that are often mistaken for the real deal. The only way to be sure you\'re buying genuine Abercrombie and Fitch gear is from one of our stores or websites.</string>
    <string name="AdidasDescription">We carry everything for your fitness needs! From basketball jerseys to hats and bags, we have it all! Kids footwear in toddler, grade-school and preschool sizes. Women\'s footwear and sport apparel, men\'s footwear and sport apparel. Shorts, sports bras and performance tees made with Playdry designed to keep your body cool and dry while you work out! Come on by today!! The sport of fitness has arrived!</string>
    <string name="AeropostaleDescription">A popular shopping destination for today\'s teenagers, Aéropostale is a leading mall-based specialty retailer that designs, markets and sells its own brand of casual, current apparel targeting 14 to 18 year-olds. Aéropostale provides their customers with high-quality fashion and basic merchandise at unquestionable value and compelling prices. Aéropostale\'s collection includes staples like their famous polos, hoodies, jeans and graphic tees as well as essentials such as dormwear, jewelry, footwear and swimwear. Aéropostale maintains their own ecommerce site, aeropostale.com, which offers extended sizes and additional Aéropostale product. The first Aéropostale store was opened in 1987.</string>
    <string name="AldoDescription">Aldo Shoes is an upscale shoe store with offerings for both men and women.</string>
    <string name="AmericanEagleDescription">AE brings you high quality, on-trend clothing, accessories and personal care products at affordable prices. AE\'s collection includes modern basics like jeans, surplus and graphic tees as well as a stylish assortment of cool accessories, outerwear, footwear and swimwear. We target men and women ages 15 to 25, but welcome individuals of all ages everywhere. Live your life. </string>
    <string name="AndersenBakeryDescription">We continue the tradition of baking pastries and breads that create authentic European taste and quality.</string>
    <string name="ArmaniExchangeDescription">Armani Exchange is the youthful label created by iconic Italian designer Giorgio Armani, offering men\'s and women\'s clothing and accessories that are inspired by the designer\'s codes of style. Armani Exchange captures the heritage of the Armani brand through a modern sensibility.</string>
    <string name="AuntieAnneDescription">Auntie Anne\'s provides 11 varieties of hot, fresh pretzel products, in sweet and zesty flavors. It\'s only natural to want to try one! And nothing goes better with your pretzel than one of our dips and our Old Fashioned Lemonade™. There\'s nothing to lose because Auntie Anne\'s has a pretzel perfect guarantee. Auntie Anne\'s guarantees you\'ll love your pretzel or they will replace it with one that you do. Yes, that may seem a little gutsy, but when you\'ve rolled, twisted and baked over a billion pretzels (that\'s 1,000,000,000) there\'s a pretty good track record. Check out www.auntieannes.com for additional information on Auntie Anne\'s.</string>
    <string name="BananaRepublicDescription">Banana Republic Factory Stores offer adult formal and casual attire for any occasion and for many needs.</string>
    <string name="BathBodyWorksDescription">Bath and Body Works is the apothecary of the 21st century. It is the authority dedicated to helping people find their own individual paths to well-being by bringing them the very best personal care products the world has to offer. Every item in more than 1,700 Bath and Body Works stores nationwide is created to help nourish the spirit, bring a sense of balance, and leave the customer feeling beautiful inside and out.</string>
    <string name="BeautyPalaceDescription">One of the premier tenants of the Great Mall. Part salon, part beauty supply extravaganza, Beauty Palace offers a large selection of products and services to make you look your best. Hair and skin care bottles from Crew, bareMinerals, Enjoy, Dermalogica, and Biolage overrun the shelves while Gladys, the beautician, performs everything from haircuts and Japanese perms to eyebrow waxing in the back.</string>
    <string name="BebeDescription">Designed for women who are passionate about fashion and their own unique style, the bebe brand combines the bold sexiness of today\'s trends, with the excitement and fun of a fast-paced lifestyle.</string>
    <string name="BedBathBeyondDescription">Founded in 1971, Bed Bath and Beyond Inc. is a nationwide chain of superstores selling predominantly better quality domestics merchandise and home furnishings. Bed Bath and Beyond combines superior service and a huge selection of items at everyday low prices within a constantly evolving shopping environment that has proven to be both fun and exciting for customers.</string>
    <string name="BevmoDescription">BevMo! stores provide an inviting and entertaining environment. Friendly, product-knowledgeable salespeople offer customers individual service and advice as they explore the store\'s vast product offering. There is a strong element of fun and discovery as customers sample wines, beers and specialty foods, often in tandem with personal appearances by noted winemakers.</string>
    <string name="BoseDescription">What makes a Bose Store experience so unique? It\'s more than just the innovative products you\'ll see. It\'s the excitement of a live demonstration, the one-on-one attention from our dedicated Sales Specialists, and the knowledge you gain with each visit. It\'s the breadth of our products, the custom installations and the ongoing support that keeps Bose customers coming back. If you\'re interested in Bose products, then come discover them like never before. Visit the Bose Store and experience something special.</string>
    <string name="BounceARamaDescription">Welcome to a world of fun. From our inflatable jumpers and slides to our exciting arcade area, we\'ve created a world your family will love. Grab the kids and come visit!</string>
    <string name="BurlingtonDescription">At Burlington Coat Factory, you\'ll find a large assortment of current, high-quality, designer and name-brand merchandise at up to 70% off department store prices. Choose from a large selection of coats, clothing, and shoes for the entire family. And don\'t forget our great assortment of linens and home décor, PLUS everything you need for baby, from baby bottles to cribs! Burlington Coat Factory -- a convenient one-stop shopping experience with the labels you love, at prices you\'ll love even more! </string>
</resources>
